Guide to the Stanford University, Bing Overseas Studies Program, Records SC0117
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- Records, Series 1
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-14/1972 (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/15-30/1972 (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-14/1972 (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/15-31/1972 (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-14/1973 (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/15-31/1973 (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-14/1973 (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/15-28/1973 (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-14/1973 (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/15-31/1973 (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-14/1973 (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/15-30/1973 (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-14/1973 (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/15-31/1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-14/1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/15-30/1973 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-14/1973 (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/15-31/1973 (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-14/1973 (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/15-31/1973 (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-14/1973 (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/15-30/1973 (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1973 (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1973 (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1973 (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1973 (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1973 (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1973 (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1974 (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1974 (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1974 (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1974 (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1974 (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1974 (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1974 (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1974 (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1974 (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1974 (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1974 (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1974 (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1974 (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1974 (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1974 (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1974 (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1974 (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1974 (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1974 (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1974 (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-16/1974 (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/17-30/1974 (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1974 (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1974 (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1975 (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1975 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1975 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1975 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1975 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1975 (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1975 (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1975 (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1975 (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1975 (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1975 (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1975 (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1975 (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1975 (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1975 (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1975 (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1975 (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1975 (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1975 (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1975 (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1975 (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-31/1975 (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1975 (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1975 (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1976 (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1976 (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1976 (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-29/1976 (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1976 (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-30/1976 (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1976 (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-31/1976 (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1976 (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1976 (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1976 (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1976 (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1976 (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1976 (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1976 (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1976 (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1976 (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1976 (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1976 (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1976 (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1976 (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1976 (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1976 (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1976 (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Britain: Harlaxton Mannor, Grantham, Lincolnshire. An Inventory and Valuation of the Pictures and Furnishings and a Schedule of Condition with Details of the Fixures and Fittings. 1965. Arnett, Calder and Twizell. Includes 7 floor plans. [Bound Volume] (Box 48, Folder 1)
- Additional Material, Accession 1984-128
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1981 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1981 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1981 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1981 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1981 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1981 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/16-30/1981 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1981 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1981 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1981 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1981 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Cables, Incoming 1981 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Cables, Outgoing 1981 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Cables, Incoming 1980 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Cables, Outgoing 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/1-15/1982 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 1/16-31/1982 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/1-15/1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 2/16-28/1982 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/1-15/1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 3/16-31/1982 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/1-15/1982 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 4/16-30/1982 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/1-15/1982 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 5/16-31/1982 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/1-15/1982 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 6/16-30/1982 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/1-15/1982 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 7/16-31/1982 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/1-15/1982 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 8/16-31/1982 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-15/1982 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 9/1-16/1982 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/1-15/1982 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 10/16-31/1982 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/1-15/1982 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 11/16-30/1982 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/1-15/1982 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Memoranda and Correspondence, Outgoing 12/16-31/1982 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Cables, Incoming 1982 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Cables, Outgoing 1982 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Additional Material, Accession 1985-023
  - Mexico Finances Correspondence 1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Finances General (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1976 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Spain: Salamanca Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - France: Paris Requisitions Correspondence 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Rome Personnel Correspondence 1973-1975 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Britain: Cliveden Personnel Correspondence 1970-1975 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Requisitions General 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Britain: Cliveden Leverhulme Trust Fund 1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Staff Benefits (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Assistant to Directors Meeting Agendas 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Assistant to Directors Application Procedure (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Assistant to Directors General (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Staff Working for Stanford Overseas (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Directors' Conference 12/1971 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Directors' Conference Minutes 12/1971 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Directors' Conference Agenda 12/1971 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Home Office Student Help 1971-1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Home Office Allocation of Responsibilities 1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Sample Appointment Letters and Job Descriptions (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Hersche Allen Trip Correspondence 6-7/1973 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Robert Walker Trip Correspondence 6-7/1973 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Corbin Smith Trip Correspondence 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Hersche Allen Trip Correspondence 6/1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Home Office Visitors 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Staff Policies and Directives 1970-1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Overseas Campus Board 1962-1970 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - President/Provost's Office Affirmative Action Program 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - President's Office Minority Program 1968-1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Provost Staff Meeting Agendas (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - President's Office General (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Provost's Office Appointments (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Provost's Office General 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Provost's Office Directives 1972 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Germany: Berlin Contract 1974-1975 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Insurance 1974 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Overseas Cash Funds 1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Stanford in Greece Proposal 1973 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Overseas Campus Budget General 1964-1965 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Overseas Campus Budget General 1969-1974 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Administration Budget 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Administration Budget 1972-1973 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Administration Budget 1973-1974 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Administration Budget 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Rome Initial Budget 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - France: Paris Requisitions Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Italy: Florence Requisitions Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Germany: Berlin Requisitions Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - France: Tours Requisitions Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Peru: Lima Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Spain: Salamanca Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Budget General 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Budget General 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Budget General 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Budget General 1962-1963 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Budget General 1964-1965 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Budget General 1973-1974 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Budget Information Memorandum 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1971-1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Budget General 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Germany: Bonn Budget 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - France: Tours Budget 1970-1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - General Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - France: Paris Requisitions Correspondence 1976-1977 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - France: Tours Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1965-1966 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1967-1968 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Italy Requisitions Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Germany: Berlin Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Germany: Berlin Requisitions Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Austria: Vienna Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Austria: Vienna Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Britain: Cliveden Requisitions Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Italy: Florence Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Germany: Bonn Requisitions Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Germany: Bonn Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Germany: Bonn Requisitions Correspondence 1975-1976 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Italy: Rome Requisitions Correspondence 1970-1972 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - France: Tours Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - France: Tours Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - France: Tours Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - General Requisitions 1973-1974 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - General Requisitions 1974-1975 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Mexico Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Mexico Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Germany: Hamburg Finances 1964-1970 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Finances General 1957-1972 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Sikes Loan Fund 1961-1974 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Austria: Vienna Panhans Contract 1967 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - France: Tours Correspondence 1968 (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - France: Tours Correspondence 1969 (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Italy: Rome Correspondence 1969 (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Capital Expenditures 1972 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Italy: Rome Finances 1974 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Rome Finances 1968 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Mexico Correspondence 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Mei Mei Cheng Memorial Fund 1967 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Directors' Conference Minutes 10/1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Directors' Conference Agenda 10/1970 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Directors' Conference Minutes 7/1969 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Directors' Conference Agenda 7/1969 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Directors' Conference Agenda 11/1966 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Directors' Conference Agenda 1/1965 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Directors' Conference Agenda 11/1967 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Directors Conference Minutes 11/1967 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Directors' Conference Minutes 11/1966 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Directors' Conference Minutes 1/1965 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Memoranda to Directors 1973-1975 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1972-1973 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1971-1972 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Policy and Procedure Home Office Memoranda 1971 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Policy and Procedure Home Office Memoranda 1970-1971 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1969-1970 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1968-1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1967-1968 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Policy and Procedure Memoranda to Directors 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Policy and Procedure Home Office Memoranda 1965-1966 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Policy and Procedure Home Office Memoranda 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Policy and Procedure Home Office Memoranda 1967-1968 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Policy and Procedure Home Office Memoranda 1969-1970 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Closure 1976-1977 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - France: Tours Personnel Correspondence 1970-1976 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Germany: Berlin Personnel Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Austria: Vienna Personnel Correspondence 19701974 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Spain: Salamanca Personnel Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Mexico Personnel Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Personnel Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Requisitions Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Personnel Correspondence 1971-1972 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Bank Contract 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Requisitions Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Personnel Correspondence 1974-1975 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Budget 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Personnel Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Requisitions Correspondence 1973-1974 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Requisitions Correspondence 1972-1973 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Additional Material, Accession 1985-110
  - Mexico Budget 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Rome Finances 1966-1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - France: Tours Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - France: Paris Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - France: Tours Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - France: Paris Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Spain: Salamanca Budget 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Germany: Berlin Budget 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Provost's Office Overseas Budget 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Provost's Office Overseas Budget 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Provost's Office Overseas Budget 1965-1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Directors' Conference Minutes 1/1974 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Summer Session Proposal 1974 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - France: Paris Correspondence 1974 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Austria: Vienna BAP IV 1972 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Budget Information for Students 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Germany: Beutelsbach Planning, with photographs 1973 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Germany: Berlin Proposal 1975 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Assistants and Secretarial Staff 1960-1973 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Austria: Vienna BAP III 1972 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Administration Budget 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - General Budget Salaries 1981-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Britain: Cliveden Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Italy: Rome Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Italy: Florence Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Austria: Vienna Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - France: Paris Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Israel: Haifa Budget 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 6)